TUAN ANH BUI LE

DEVOPS ENGINEER



Contacts

- **†** 27/08/2001
- Male
- (+84) 937826135
- builetuananh2708@gmail.com
- 1 https://www.builetuananh.name.vn
- Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Skills

Programming

- · Bash, Python, Golang, Basic C/C++
- SQL & NoSQL (PostgreSQL, MongoDB)

Technologies & Techniques

- CI/CD (GitOps): Git, Jenkins, Argo CD
- Virtualization & IaC: Terraform, Docker, Helm, Kubernetes
- Cloud/On-premises Management (Linux/AWS)
- · Monitoring: Zabbix, ELK/EFK

Soft Skills

- Teamwork & Team Leadership
- Problem Solving
- Presentation & Communication

Certifications

2023

IELTS Academic (7.0) - British Council, Cambridge ESOL, IDP Australia

Objectives

Being worked in 2 companies, with two big projects, 1 in production status, obtaining a System/Network Developer, Cloud Developer, Site Reliability Engineer, or DevOps Engineer position in a company is a short-term goal, to enhance my level and apply all knowledge in DevOps and Networking for high-quality products.

Becoming a Senior DevOps Engineer or Senior Site Reliability Engineer is a long-term goal in 3-4 years, as well as mastering new technologies, and devoting to the company where I work.

Work experience

Technical Support Engineer

JAN 2024 - MAY 2024

Microsoft Vietnam

- Act as a Microsoft Support Engineer (from Security, Compliance and Identity Management Team) to assist customers with Microsoft 365 services
- Use standard processes, implement existing diagnosis methods, and solutions/workarounds to effectively deal with more than 100 customers from across the globe to achieve problem resolution and customer satisfaction.
- Technology stack: PowerShell

Site Reliability Engineering Intern

AUG 2022 - JAN 2023

OPSWAT Vietnam

- Program, migrate and build products on cloud providers via virtualization and Infrastructure as Code (IaC)
- Test, assess and deploy a Kubernetes Event-driven Autoscaling (KEDA) solution onto products' Kubernetes clusters after 2 weeks of working with R&D team.
- Help to reduce the monthly production cost for up to **30 percent**.
- Technology stack: Docker, AWS, Terraform, Python, Kubernetes, Bash

Projects

cs101_devops

MAR 2024 - PRESENT

https://github.com/anthony2708/cs101_devops

- A Github repository for CS101 event from GDSC-HCMUS and SAB in HCMUS. Also include 90 days of DevOps campaign (2022 version).
- · Technology stack: Git, Astro (FE), Docker, Terraform, Bash
- Website: https://90days.builetuananh.name.vn/

tech-savvy

NOV 2023 - PRESENT

https://github.com/anthony2708/tech-savvy

- A Github repository for learning new technologies.
- Technology stack: Git, Golang, Docker, Terraform, Bash, Kubernetes

Additional information

- Facebook:
 - https://facebook.com/buile.tuananh/
- Github: https://github.com/anthony2708/
- · Linkedin:

https://linkedin.com/in/anthony2708/

Activities

MAR 2024

Speaker of **CS101 Session 2: Code Sync - Git's Veiled Team Symphony** - GDSC-HCMUS/SAB in HCMUS

Service Portal

JAN 2023 - JUN 2023

https://bitbucket.org/19120163/graduation/

- **Topic**: A study of Infrastructure as Code and web application deployment on Amazon Web Services.
- Received a Distinction grade (9.4 out of 10)
- Acheived the average loading time of under 500ms, and average download speed for up to 1.5Mbps, tested on 18000 concurrent users
- Reduced monthly cost of web application operation to US\$10-20
- Technology stack: AWS, Docker, Terraform, Bash, Zabbix, TypeScript
- Website: https://www.builetuananh.name.vn/services

Education

VNUHCM - University of Science

SEP 2019 - JULY 2023

Information Technology

- · Major: Computer Networking & Telecommunications
- Overall GPA: 7.96/10.

© topcv.vn